[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "William Friedkin was born in Chicago. Illinois in 1935. He became fascinated with movies after watching this film as a boy.", "correct_answer": "Citizen Kane", "incorrect_answers": ["The Lady from Shanghai", "The Man with the Golden Arm", "Rio Bravo"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Nowadays, sugar is used in science and manufacturing as what?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Preservative", "Bulking agent", "Sweetener"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This friend of Vincent Van Gogh and once-successful stockbroker produced the famous work, The Yellow Christ.", "correct_answer": "Gauguin", "incorrect_answers": ["Cezanne", "Matisse", "Pisarro"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What year was Roy Del Ruths movie The Alligator People released?", "correct_answer": "1959", "incorrect_answers": ["1955", "1957", "1956"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What animals do wolves generally prefer to feed on?", "correct_answer": "Ungulates", "incorrect_answers": ["Rodents", "Birds", "Fish"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What 1978 movie received the Oscar for Best Picture at the 51st Academy Awards ceremony?", "correct_answer": "The Deer Hunter", "incorrect_answers": ["Coming Home", "Midnight Express", "Heaven Can Wait"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "At what temperature is the Fahrenheit temperature equal the Celsius temperature?", "correct_answer": "-40 degrees", "incorrect_answers": ["0 degrees", "4 degrees", "-4 degrees"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie The World Is Not Enough, the bullet is located in what part of Renards body?", "correct_answer": "In his brain", "incorrect_answers": ["In his heart", "In his lung", "In his hand"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what year was the word bastard first used on TV?", "correct_answer": "1974", "incorrect_answers": ["1964", "1960", "1984"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Easter Island, an island in the south Pacific Ocean, is a territory of which country?", "correct_answer": "Chile", "incorrect_answers": ["The United States", "Peru", "Ecuador"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The ghost of Archbishop of Canterbury Thomas Becket appeared during the construction of the Twin Towers in the 1920s.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many legs does a dragonfly have?", "correct_answer": "6", "incorrect_answers": ["8", "0", "4"]}]